<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on </title>
    <link>https://mrl-workshop.github.io/iclr-2023/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://mrl-workshop.github.io/iclr-2023/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Call for Papers</title>
      <link>https://mrl-workshop.github.io/iclr-2023/call-for-papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrl-workshop.github.io/iclr-2023/call-for-papers/</guid>
      <description>Call for Papers We welcome submissions related to any aspects of multimodal representation learning, including but not limited to:
Properties of multimodal representations. Insights on interactions across modalities. Novel applications regarding the nature and number of modalities. In particular, we encourage submission that address the following questions:
Representation: How do we identify useful properties of multimodal representations? What semantic information is encoded in the learned representations? How does the geometry of the representation space affect the quality of the learned representations?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Formatting Instructions</title>
      <link>https://mrl-workshop.github.io/iclr-2023/formatting-instructions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrl-workshop.github.io/iclr-2023/formatting-instructions/</guid>
      <description>Formatting Instructions Style &amp;amp; Author Instructions Submissions should be formatted using the ICLR 2023 latex template and formatting instructions. Papers must be submitted as a PDF file and there will be a strict upper limit of 4 pages for the main text, which should include all main results, figures, and tables. This page limit applies to both the initial and final camera ready version., including all main results, figures, and tables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invited Speakers</title>
      <link>https://mrl-workshop.github.io/iclr-2023/speakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrl-workshop.github.io/iclr-2023/speakers/</guid>
      <description>Invited Speakers Siddharth Narayanaswamy Zeynep Akata Arsha Nagrani Paul Pu Liang Kristen Grauman </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organizers</title>
      <link>https://mrl-workshop.github.io/iclr-2023/organizers-reviewers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrl-workshop.github.io/iclr-2023/organizers-reviewers/</guid>
      <description>Organizers Adrián Javaloy Miguel Vasco Petra Poklukar Yuge Shi Imant Daunhawer Danica Kragic Isabel Valera Contact For any questions or comments, please contact us at mrl.workshop.2023@gmail.com.
Acknowledgements We acknowledge and greatly appreciate the help of all reviewers and members of the program committee who made this workshop possible.
Abhishek Sinha Waymo AJ Piergiovanni Google Alain Ryser ETH Zurich Aleksandr Panov Artificial Intelligence Research Institute Alexander Marx ETH Zurich Alexey Kovalev Artificial Intelligence Research Institute Alice Bizeul ETH Zurich Amro Kamal Mohamed Abbas &amp;nbsp The African Institute For Mathematical Sciences Anthony Zhe Liu University of Michigan Batuhan Koyuncu Saarland University Chaerin Kong Seoul National University Christopher Wang MIT CSAIL Colin Conwell Harvard University Dan Ruta University of Surrey Daniel Barrejon Universidad Carlos III de Madrid Daphné Chopard ETH Zurich Dmitry Yudin Artificial Intelligence Research Intsitute Dota Tianai Dong Max Planck Institute for Psycholinguistics Emanuele Palumbo ETH Zurich Fábio Vital Instituto Superior Técnico, Lisboa Farah Shamout New York University Francisco S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviewers</title>
      <link>https://mrl-workshop.github.io/iclr-2023/reviewers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrl-workshop.github.io/iclr-2023/reviewers/</guid>
      <description>Reviewers Adam Li, Columbia University
Alexander Hägele, ETHZ - ETH Zurich
Biwei Huang, Carnegie Mellon University
Bohdan Kivva, University of Chicago
Bryon Aragam, University of Chicago
Chandler Squires, Massachusetts Institute of Technology
Cian Eastwood, University of Edinburgh
Daniel Malinsky, Johns Hopkins University
Davide Talon, Università degli Studi di Genova, Istituto Italiano di Tecnologia
Dhanya Sridhar, Université de Montréal and Mila-Quebec AI Institute
Furui Liu, Huawei Technologies Ltd.
Gargi Balasubramaniam, University of Illinois, Urbana Champaign</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule and Format</title>
      <link>https://mrl-workshop.github.io/iclr-2023/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrl-workshop.github.io/iclr-2023/schedule/</guid>
      <description>Preliminary Workshop Schedule Legend: invited · contributed · poster · break Time Program Format 09:00 - 09:10 Introduction and Opening Remarks Live 09:10 - 09:40 Invited Talk 1: Zeynep Akata Live 09:45 - 10:15 Contributed Talk 1 &amp; 2 15mins pre-recorded talk each 10:20 - 10:50 Invited Talk 2: N. Siddharth Live 10:50 - 11:00 Coffee break - 11:00 - 12:00 Poster Talk Session 1 20mins pre-recorded talks + 40mins poster session 12:00 - 13:30 Lunch break - 13:30 - 14:00 Invited Talk 3: Paul Liang Live 14:00 - 15:00 Poster Talk Session 2 20mins pre-recorded talks + 40mins poster session 15:00 - 15:10 Coffee break - 15:10 - 15:40 Contributed Talk 3 &amp; 4 15mins pre-recorded talk each 15:45 - 16:15 Invited Talk 4: Arsha Nagrani Live 16:20 - 16:50 Invited Talk 5: Kristen Grauman Live 16:50 - 17:00 Coffee break - 17:00 - 17:45 Panel Discussion Live 17:45 - 18:00 Closing Remarks Live All times according to current local time in Kigali, Rwanda (GMT+2).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
